# Tyme Bleyaert Full-Stack .NET developer

Last update: February 22, 2024

Residence	♠ Eeklo, Belgium
LinkedIn	in <u>LinkedIn</u>
Email	@ tyme.bleyaert@gmail.com

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

https://Tyme-Bleyaert.github.io/cv

Full-stack .NET developer with over 2 years of experience. In the last years, I worked with: Winforms / WPF / Angular / Blazor / ASP.Net / DevExtreme for frontend, and for backend: Windows services / Entity Framework / ADO / RDO / SQL and Blazor server.

## **Professional Experience**

December 2023 - Present

## De Jaeger Automation Byba

Senior full-stack .NET developer

July 2021 - November 2023

### De Jaeger Automation Byba

Full-stack .NET developer



Working on the <u>ProSuite</u> framework. Developed a web based guidance application using Blazor and web API, ensuring scalability and performance. Improved stability and performance of the already existing framework and products.

#### Responsibilities:

- · Performing code reviews
- · Mentoring junior developers
- · Promoting best coding practices
- · Maintaining build and release pipelines
- Analyzing product performance issue
- · Designing and developing new products

#### Reference(s):

Ronald Van Laerebeke coo +32 (0)9 379 50 52

September 2016 - August 2020

## Various temporary positions

Laborer

## **Education**

.NET Developer C# - VDAB [18/11/2020 - 04/07/2021]
Basic IT - VDAB [18/08/2020 - 17/11/2020]
Game Development - Howest Kortrijk [2015 - 2016]
Web Development - Syntra West [2014 - 2015]
Accounting & Informatics - GO! Atheneum Maldegem [2014]

## **Skills**

















## **Additional Experience**

Passionate about working on my .NET library and providing assistance to other developers on open source projects (GitHub).

